[{"id": 2605, "question": "As the Internet's influence grows, the potential for danger also escalates . One of these dangers is from cyber-bullying. Cyber-bullying is repeatedly hurting someone else through the use of technology. It consists of sending or posting cruel messages, photos, or videos on the Internet or other electronic media with the intent of damaging the reputation of the target. Imagine being a 13-year-old girl discovering a cell phone picture of her changing clothes for gym class has been sent to all her classmates. Or imagine being an 11-year-old boy who is scared to go to school because an unknown bully sent him an instant message saying that he is so fat that he should kill himself. Cases such as these are happening every day, leading kids to be depressed and unable to concentrate. Worse yet, par...\n\nQ: What does the author think of the cyber-bullying?", "options": ["It is not as harmful as people think.", "It is too complex a problem to settle.", "It will not affect the relationship between classmates.", "It can be stopped through our efforts."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2584, "question": "According to the dictionary definition of 'create',ordinary people are creative every day. To create means to bring into being,to cause to exist something each of us does daily. We are creative whenever we look at or think about something in a new way. First,this includes an awareness of our surroundings. It means using all of our senses to become aware of our world. This may be as simple as being aware of color1 and texture ,as well as taste, when we plan a meal. Above all,it is the ability to notice things that others might miss. A second part of creativity is an ability to see relationships among things. If we believe the expression,there is nothing new under the sun,the creativity is remaking or recombining the old in new ways. For example,we might do this by finding a more effective w...\n\nQ: Which of the following activities is NOT a creative one according to the passage?", "options": ["To prepare for a meal.", "To arrange the furniture in a special way.", "To buy some books from a bookstore.", "To write a letter with the computer."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 574, "question": "In 1955, a man named Raymond Kroc entered a partnership with two brothers named Mcdonald. They operated a popular restaurant in California which sold food that was easy to prepare and serve quickly. Hamburgers, French fries, and cold drinks were the main foods on the limited menu. Kroc opened similar eating places under the same name, \"McDonald's\" and they were a quick success. He later took over the company and today it is one of the most famous and successful \"fast-food\" chains in America and the world. Why was his idea so successful? Probably the most important reason was that his timing was right. In the 1950s, most married women stayed home to keep house and take care of their children. During the 1960s, the movement for equality between men and women and an economy that needed more f...\n\nQ: We can infer from the passage that   _  .", "options": ["natural foods can also be found in McDonald's", "many married women in America returned to work in the 1960s", "McDonald's fast food is popular among the young", "divorce caused people to change their eating habits"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1760, "question": "I'm part of the Roots & Shoots program founded by Dr. Jane Goodall. The program is intended to make and promote positive changes in the world. As Dr. Goodall says, \"What you do makes a difference, and you have to decide what kind of difference you want to make.\" In Bulgaria, where I live, homeless dogs are everywhere. Many people here turn a blind eye to them. But I cannot ignore the life of a street dog whenever I see one wandering in the street, looking for something to eat. That's why I'm no longer a food waster. When I see wasted food, I always think of a hungry dog climbing to garbage bins, searching for food that people have thrown there. When eating in a restaurant, I'm not afraid to take leftover food to feed stray cats or dogs. A week ago, I saw a homeless dog around the garbage b...\n\nQ: The author took the leftover fish with him to   _  .", "options": ["eat it when he was hungry", "feed a homeless dog he met", "look for more homeless animals", "set an example to those who throw away food"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 3354, "question": "Iceland, an island just south of the Arctic Circle, has fairly mild winters, thanks to warm ocean currents. Time your vacation here during the winter months to take advantage of off-season deals. Off-season means good deals on flights, hotels and tours. You may also find that the locals are a bit friendlier and more welcoming when tourists aren't arriving in crowds. In the winter months, there are less than seven hours of daylight; thus, chances are good you'll catch sight of the northern lights. Sunsets are also beautiful at this time, making for some great photo opportunities. In Iceland, winter is the perfect time to hike glaciers, go ice climbing, explore caves made out of hardened lava and much more. One of the most popular activities is off-roading in a specially-equipped \"super jeep...\n\nQ: According to this article, why are you more likely to see the northern lights in the winter?", "options": ["They move from rural areas to cities.", "The weather is more stable at that time.", "They're a special feature of many festivals.", "The sky is dark for longer periods then."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 235, "question": "Sociable people seem to gain extra rewards from their relationships by feeling less stressed, taking better care of themselves and having less risky lifestyles, they claim. A review of studies into the impact of relationships on health found that people had a 50% better survival rate if they belonged to a wider social group. Psychologist Holt-Lunstad's team reviewed 148 studies that observed the social activities and health of 308,849 people over an average of 7.5 years. From these they worked out how death rates varied depending on how sociable a person was. Being lonely and isolated was as bad for a person's health as smoking 15 cigarettes a day or being an alcoholic. It was as harmful as not exercising and twice as bad for the health as being very fat. Holt-Lunstad said friends and fami...\n\nQ: According to the text, which of the following is NOT a benefit of being sociable people?", "options": ["Getting better in the state of heath.", "Losing weight more easily.", "Taking better care of themselves.", "Having more safe lifestyles."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 3229, "question": "Global warming is causing more than 300,000 deaths and about $125 billion in economic losses each year, according to a report by the Global Humanitarian Forum, an organization led by Annan, the former United Nations secretary general. The report, to be released Friday, analyzed data and existing studies of health, disaster, population and economic trends. It found that human-influenced climate change was raising the global death rates from illnesses including malnutrition and heat-related health problems. But even before its release, the report drew criticism from some experts on climate and risk, who questioned its methods and conclusions. Along with the deaths, the report said that the lives of 325 million people, primarily in poor countries, were being seriously affected by climate chan...\n\nQ: What does Dr. Pielke say about the Forum's report?", "options": ["Its statistics look embarrassing.", "It is invalid in terms of methodology.", "It deserves our closest attention.", "Its conclusion is purposely exaggerated."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2365, "question": "All the oceans of the world will be dead in the future unless action is taken at once. How can this happen? We have already seen that people allow all sorts of waste products to flow into the sea. It is almost impossible to measure how much waste water and industrial waste in our oceans, but we can find out how much oil is poured into them legally and illegally. It is illegal to pour oil into the sea close to the shore, but when a ship is many miles out to sea, there are no such rules. Scientists have different ideas as to the amount of oil putting into the sea, but the lowest figure for oil poured in European waters alone is nearly 200 000 tons every year. Some people say the figure could be ten times as high. It is not only our coasts that suffer from oil pollution. Many shell fish, for ...\n\nQ: This passage is mainly about  _  .", "options": ["pollution in the oceans", "oil pollution in the waters", "the amounts of poison in shell fish", "the amounts of oil in the sea"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2532, "question": "As computers become more popular in China , Chinese people are increasingly relying on computer keyboards to input Chinese characters . But if they use the computer too much , they may end up forgetting the exact strokes of each Chinese character when writing on paper . Experts suggest people , especially students , write by hand more . Do you write by hand more or type more ? In Beijing , students start using a computer as early as primary school . And computer dependence is more widespread among university students . Almost all their assignments and essays are typed on a computer . All the students interviewed say they usually use a computer . It's faster and easier to correct if using a computer . And that's why computers are being applied more and more often to modern education . But w...\n\nQ: The students interviewed prefer to write using a computer mainly because    _    .", "options": ["they are usually asked to email their homework and essays", "they can correct the mistakes they make quickly and conveniently", "they find it not easy to remember how to write a character", "computers have become a trend and fashion in China"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1261, "question": "A new collection of photos brings an unsuccessful Antarctic voyage back to life. Frank Hurley's pictures would be outstanding----undoubtedly first-rate photo-journalism---if they had been made last week. In fact, they were shot from 1914 through 1916, most of them after a disastrous shipwreck , by a cameraman who had no reasonable expectation of survival. Many of the images were stored in an ice chest, under freezing water, in the damaged wooden ship. The ship was the Endurance, a small, tight, Norwegian-built three-master that was intended to take Sir Ernest Shackleton and a small crew of seamen and scientists, 27 men in all, to the southernmost shore of Antarctica's Weddell Sea. From that point Shackleton wanted to force a passage by dog sled across the continent. The journey was intende...\n\nQ: What does Alexander think was the purpose of the 1914 voyage?", "options": ["Artistic creation", "Scientific research", "Money making", "Treasure hunting"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2166, "question": "Many people earn their living with their hands. Ed earns his living with his feet! And a very good living it is, too. Ed's story began in a very small town in Brazil. His father and mother were very poor. Seven people lived in their tiny house. Ed's father often played football. Little Ed wanted to play football too. So his father made a soft ball for him to kick. It was a sock filled with soft materials. The little boy kicked it every day. At last Ed learned to kick a real football. By the time he was 11, he played football very well. One day Ed was playing with some men. A man passing by saw how fast the boy ran. He stopped to watch. How well Ed kicked the ball! After the game, the man called Ed to him. \"My name is Mr. Dee,\" he said. \"I used to play football for a living. Will you let me...\n\nQ: What can we know about Mr. Dee from the text?", "options": ["He joined the Santos Football Club.", "He and Ed used to live in the same town.", "He had been the best football player in Brazil.", "He happened to find a very good football player."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 141, "question": "In 1947 a group of famous people from the art world headed by an Austrian conductor decided to hold an intemational festival of music,dance and theatre in Edinburgh. The idea was to reunite Europe after the Second World War. At the same time, the \"Fringe\" appeared as a challenge to the official festival.Eight theatre groups turned up uninvited in 1947,in the belief that everyone should have the right to perform,and they did so in a public house disused for years. Soon,groups of studentsfirstly from Edinburgh University, and later from the universities of Oxford and Cambridge,Durham and Birmingham were making the journey to the Scottish capital each summer to perform theatre by little-known writers of plays in small church halls to the people of Edinburgh. Today the \"Fringe\",once less recog...\n\nQ: Point was the purpose of Edinburgh Festival at he beginning?", "options": ["To bring Europe together again.", "To honor heroes of World War 11.", "To introduce young theatre groups.", "To attract great artists from Europe."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2668, "question": "One day while shopping in a small town in southern California,it was my misfortune to be approached by a clerk whose personality conflicted with mine. He seemed most unfriendly and not at all concerned about my intended purchase. I bought nothing,and marched angrily out of the store. My hostility toward that clerk increased with each step. On the outside,standing by the road,was a darkskinned young man in his early twenties. His expressive brown eyes met and held mine,and in the next instant a beautiful, dazzling smile covered his face. I gave way immediately. The magnetic power of that smile dissolved all bitterness within me,and I found the muscles in my own face happily responding . \"Beautiful day,isn't it?\"I remarked,in passing. Then,I turned back.\"I really owe you a debt of gratitude ...\n\nQ: Why did the author leave the store angrily?", "options": ["The clerk treated him unkindly.", "He couldn't buy what he wanted.", "The clerk didn't speak English.", "The store's goods were too dear."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2370, "question": "Star Wars Millennium Falcon This is a gift that, if we're being honest, many dads want to own for themselves. This huge ship is the greatest Star Wars toy. It lights up and makes some noises. Every boy from 3 to 53 will absolutely like it, if they can find room for it. I dare say even a few grandfathers might go for it. Biscuit--the Loving Pup You may clearly know that a pet can be a great thing to a child's development but you probably don't think that you can take care of a dog properly. The robot dog Biscuit is less likely to the disorder of your house and except for a few dead batteries, won't leave any surprises on the floor. It will be a good playmate for your kids. JVC KD-10 Headphones It's increasingly common for kids to enjoy themselves on long journeys with a portable DVD player ...\n\nQ: Which of the gifts is designed mainly for girls?", "options": ["Holz Wooden Airport.", "Sparrow-kids Routemaster Kit", "Star Wars Millennium Falcon.", "Biscuit--the Loving Pup."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 551, "question": "Elena Kagan has reached a lifelong goal:becoming a Justice on the United States Supreme Court.The U.S. Senate confirmed Kagan on Thursday by a vote of 6337.She replaces Justice John Paul Stevens,who retired in June. Kagan will take a sacred oath to uphold the Constitution of the United States on Saturday at a swearingin ceremony.The new Justice will bring the number of women sitting on the nation's highest court to three.Kagan joins Justices Ruth Bader Ginsburg and Sonia Sotomayor--all three New Yorkers. Kagan is the fourth woman in history to sit on the Supreme Court.Justice Sandra Day O'Connor was the first female Justice.She was appointed by President Ronald Reagan and served from 1981 to 2006. Kagan,who is 50 years old,is the second Justice appointed by President Barack Obama.(He appoi...\n\nQ: This text must be taken from   _  .", "options": ["a storybook", "a textbook", "a newspaper", "a biography of famous people"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 3031, "question": "A news release is a tool of communication,through which information is passed to even the farthest end of the world.It keeps us well informed of the happenings of the world which would otherwise remain unknown. When writing a news release,keep in mind that the media receive hundreds of releases every day.Try to follow these guidelines:Keep it short and professional.Come up with a _ headline that will grasp someone's attention.Sometimes the title will take more time to come up with than writing the release.That's okay-the headline could be critical for getting an event covered! Cover the 5 W's in your first paragraph.Those are who you are; what you are doing;where,when you are doing;why you are doing it,which help us understand the details about the event.Besides,any opinions in the news re...\n\nQ: Which of the following is RIGHT according to the passage?", "options": ["A news release is more important than any other medium.", "Any opinions in the news release should have quotations.", "The main task of the spokesperson is to correct the mistakes by the writer.", "Lacking experience,the person who writes the release may make mistakes."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 3459, "question": "I was with a group of businessmen, and we were dealing with a question--What is a good person? At a certain point during the discussion, one of the students--a young man of about thirty--described an event that happened at Christmas. He and his five-year-old son were decorating the Christmas tree, and a little boy came to the front door begging. If you ever visit Mexico, you will see that the people there take begging as nothing to get upset about and nothing to get embarrassed by. So, this little boy came to the door, a boy about the same age as my student's son. The father and the son went to the front door, and the father went back with his five-year-old son and said to him, \"Give him one of your toys.\" At the words, the little boy quickly picked up some toy, and his father said to him,...\n\nQ: According to the writer, being a good person means   _  .", "options": ["having the courage to correct his/her mistakes", "being friendly to beggars", "being ready to give", "being able to teach children to tell right from wrong"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2927, "question": "Kodak's decision to apply for bankruptcy protection is a sad, though not unexpected, turning point for a leading American corporation that pioneered consumer photography and dominated the film market for decades, but finally failed to adapt to the digital revolution. Although many attribute Kodak's downfall to \"complacency ,\" that explanation doesn't admit the efforts with which the company went to reinvent itself. Decades ago, Kodak invented the first digital camera in 1975 -- but in a fateful decision, the company chose to focus on its traditional film business. Large companies have a difficult time switching into new markets. For example, although Kodak predicted the rise of digital photography, its culture was too rooted in the successes of the past to fully welcome the future. In the ...\n\nQ: What do we learn about Kodak?", "options": ["It went bankrupt all of a sudden.", "It is approaching its downfall.", "It is playing a dominant role in the film market.", "It started the digital revolution in the film industry."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2942, "question": "Although most weddings follow long-held traditions, there's still room for American individualism. For example, the usual place for a wedding is in a church. But some people get married outdoors in a scenic spot. A few even have the ceremony while skydiving or riding on horseback! The couple may invite hundreds of people or just a few close friends. They choose their own style of colors, decorations and music during the ceremony. But some things rarely change. The bride usually wears a beautiful long white wedding dress. She traditionally wears \"something old, something new, something borrowed and something blue.\" The groom wears a formal suit. Several close friends participate in the ceremony as attendants, including the best man and the maid of honor. As the ceremony begins, the groom an...\n\nQ: According to the passage, which of the following is TRUE?", "options": ["The best man is the one to marry the maid of honor.", "The wedding reception is a party after the wedding ceremony.", "The newlyweds always take a honeymoon in their own cars.", "Many couples take a vacation trip before the wedding."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1940, "question": "Mary went out at night. She never forgot the night when she met a robber many years ago. That evening, she was invited to a birthday party which lasted until two o'clock in the morning. Without company Mary walked along the quiet street. Suddenly from the shadow of a dark building a tall man with a sharp knife in his right hand ran out at her. \"Good evening, lady,\" the man said in a low voice, \"I don't think you wish to die here.\" \"What do you want?\" Mary asked. \"Your earrings .Take them off!\" Slowly Mary's eyes looked down. She tried to cover her necklace with the collar of her overcoat while she used the other hand to take off both of her earrings, and then she quickly threw them on the ground. \"Take them and let me go.\" she said. The robber looked at her only feeling uncertain. He saw t...\n\nQ: She tried to protect the necklace because   _  .", "options": ["she didn't want to lose it", "it was more important", "she liked it better than earrings", "she would rather have the necklace lost"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1287, "question": "Not having done physical exercise for some time, I found myself a little low-spirited and couldn't study efficiently, so I decided to do some running the next day. At 6:15 the next morning, my alarm clock rang. Unwilling to rise from my bed, I turned it off and went back to sleep. However, 5 minutes later, I struggled to get up. After washing and brushing, I had my sneakers on and went out. Wow! The air was so fresh that I couldn't help breathing it deeply. I stretched my arms and legs, then started to run. I found all things around me were so attractive. Look, the branches were waving, as if they were welcoming me; the blossoming flowers were bowing, with shyness, just like girls. Listen, the wind was whispering, as if to say \"come on, girl\". What's more interesting was those two birds, p...\n\nQ: Which of the following statements is NOT true according to the passage?", "options": ["The writer rose immediately after the clock went off.", "The writer enjoyed the singing of the two birds.", "The writer did some warm-up exercises before running.", "The writer felt refreshed after doing some running in the morning."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 1831, "question": "Being young is great. Most of the parts of your body still work great, you have a full head of hair, you're energetic, and you have a world of opportunity in front of you. However, there's going to come a time when you start to get older. And as you get older, you'll have new responsibilities, complete independence, and perhaps most importantly, less time to recover from mistakes. You see, we all make mistakes in life. Maybe you spent more money than you should have on a car, you passed up on a great job opportunity, or you didn't try as hard as you could have in school. It's a part of life and we learn from it. But there are certain mistakes that are much better made while you're still young and have plenty of time to recover. I'm definitely not telling you that you should purposely go ou...\n\nQ: You can bounce around a little bit and find out what you want to do. \"Bounce\" in this sentence is most similar in meaning to   _  .", "options": ["My father would burst into the kitchen bouncing a football.", "The wind was bouncing the branches of the big oak trees.", "I was an army brat, I always bounced a lot when I was young", "The ex-boxer's job is to bounce people who want to enter this private club."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 3100, "question": "An English saying goes: \" _ \" That means we should relax after a day's hard work or we'll be unhealthy. Many students know that if they want to get ideal jobs with good salaries, they must do well in high school so they can enter good universities. Therefore, they spend all day studying without time to relax. However, not all students can go to top universities even if they work very hard. Students are pressurized by parents and teachers who are just concerned about their studies and exam scores while ignoring their hobbies and individual differences. As a result, students are forces to work harder and harder. Furthermore, there is pressure coming from students themselves. They realize they have a slim chance of getting into a top university as competition is fierce. So, they put a lot of ...\n\nQ: What is the passage mainly about?", "options": ["What to do to relax yourself.", "The serous situation for the poor students.", "Some problems caused by the misunderstanding of learning.", "How to be a healthy and successful learner."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1707, "question": "Everyone, please think of your biggest personal goal. For real - you can take a second. You've got to feel this to learn it. Take a few seconds and think of your personal biggest goal, okay? Imagine deciding right now that you're going to do it. Imagine telling someone that you meet today what you're going to do. Imagine their congratulations and their high image of you. Doesn't it feel good to say it out loud? Don't you feel one step closer already, like it's already becoming part of your identity? Well, bad news: you should have kept your mouth shut, because that good feeling now will make you less likely to do it. Repeated psychology tests have proved that telling someone your goal makes it less likely to happen. Any time you have a goal, there are some steps that need to be done, some ...\n\nQ: What is the article mainly about?", "options": ["The importance of having personal goals.", "Tips on achieving your personal goals.", "Studies on why people tend to keep their personal goals secret.", "Why it's not necessarily wise to announce your personal goals to others."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2622, "question": "The story of Juno and Lucas is one of the most touching stories about the amazing relationship between humans and their companion animals. Juno is a Belgian Malinois . The dog was beautiful but was given up by its owners, as they did not want to take on the responsibility. Lucas, a little boy, had a strange illness, a condition that stops the body's ability to process enzymes .As his life continues, he will lose the ability to speak and his physical and mental abilities will degrade till he is left in a vegetative state. The average life expectancy for the patients is 15 years. Chester, the boy's father, wanted his child to enjoy his life on earth as much as possible and looked into getting a service dog for the child. However, Lucas wasn't a good candidate due to his deteriorating abiliti...\n\nQ: Chester wanted to find a service dog to   _  .", "options": ["protect Lucas from being injured", "help the boy recover from the disease", "accompany Lucas to enjoy his time left", "show their love for the beautiful dog"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2181, "question": "The owner of an Alabama Chinese restaurant named \"Good Friend\" shot at a customer who complained about a fly in her eggroll Thursday night. The bullet narrowly missed 20-year-old Birmingham resident Jatari Walker who told the Daily News she is scarred by the entire experience. \"I can't sleep,\" she said Saturday afternoon. \"And since it happened I've had no appetite.\" Walker ordered a combination platter and eggroll from the Good Friend Chinese and Seafood Restaurant on Dennison Ave. Thursday evening. After paying her $7 bill she went back to her car and discovered a fly inside. \"I thought I need to take this back,\" she said. The customer went back and asked for a repayment and said the owner Chun HinChing, 52, was unhappy with her because she announced her discovery in front of other custo...\n\nQ: Why did Walker go back to the restaurant after buying the food?", "options": ["Because she left her car key in the restaurant.", "Because she discovered a fly in the egg roll.", "Because she forgot to take the combination platter.", "Because she found the owner charged her too much."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 3139, "question": "Harry potter and The Hunger Games haven't been big hits for nothing. Lots of teens still read quite a lot. But a study shows a clear decrease over time. Nearly half of 17-year-olds say they read for pleasure no more than one or two times a year. That's way down from ten years ago. The digital revolution means there are more platforms than ever to read on. Jim Steyer has been studying the effect of technology on children. He has four kids and has seen the trend most with his 16-year-old. \"I start to see it in our 10-year-old as well, because he is reading less and less, and more and more attracted to some of the digital media platforms that he has access to, and that he didn't have access to when he was 6 or 7 years old,\" he says. The studies don't say that kids are reading less because the...\n\nQ: What statement may Kathryn Zickuhr agree to?", "options": ["Kids are easily distracted on the Internet.", "Most kids pretend to be doing online reading.", "Most kids like to read on a smartphone or tablet.", "Kids rarely use the Internet to do serious research."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 358, "question": "America's child movie star Shirley Temple Black died late Monday evening at the age of 85. Her fans in China are also deeply saddened. Temple is just one example of movie stars that China adored, and still adores. Here's our editor's pick of the top movie stars who have influenced China. 1. Sylvester Stallone Oh, Rambo! The first strong American man that China knew. His accented English, easily recognizable even for someone who doesn't speak English, and his eyes that never seemed to smile, makes him someone whom cannot be forgotten. He represented the strong American image, and even stirred a boxing and bodybuilding fever in China. 2.Charlie Chaplin (April 16, 1889 - December 25, 1977) In the 20th century, it is not too much to say that Einstein made the greatest contributions to science,...\n\nQ: In which part can we most probably read this passage?", "options": ["Art", "Columns", "Music & Theater", "Film &TV"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 154, "question": "It is well known that Einstein was the father of the famous Theory of Relativity. But do you know it owes a great deal to Marits, Einstein's former wife? In 1896, 17-year-old Einstein went to Zurich to study physics. There he met a girl from Hungary. They studied in the same class. The same interest brought the two together and the young man fell in love with Marits. In 1903, when Einstein was 24 years old, he married Marits, who was 4 years older than he. After their marriage, Einstein devoted himself to the research of the great theory. To give her husband more help, Marits gave up her own work, and became a good wife and assistant. She tried her best to encourage him whenever possible and she was sure that her husband would succeed. They often discussed the theory while walking outside ...\n\nQ: Einstein fell in love with Marits mainly because they   _  .", "options": ["were in the same school", "wanted to do research together", "had the same interest", "came from different countries"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1167, "question": "Eva Mozes Kor has good reasons to look down upon Oskar Groning. When she and her twin sister, Miriam, arrived in the Auschwitz death camp, they were met by Josef Mengele and became part of the cruel scientist's experiments. Groning was a junior squad leader at the camp. While Groning could argue he was not directly responsible for procedures carried out on twins,nor for the mass murder of so many others, he played a critical role in the effort to kill Jews. After the war Groning led an ordinary, quiet life until he became alarmed by the rise of Holocaust deniers. He went public with his role and in September 2014 was charged as an accessory to murder. When Groning went on trial in April 2015, Eva Mozes Kor was called as a witness. After her session, she walked straight up to the 93-year-ol...\n\nQ: Facing Holocaust deniers again, Groning felt   _            .", "options": ["amazed", "upset", "fearful", "quiet"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 1494, "question": "The SAT is one of two major tests for the entrance to American colleges and universities. The other test is called the ACT. More than 2 million students take the SAT yearly, including about 100,000 foreign students. The organization of the SAT will change the entrance test in 2016. The College Board announced that the new SAT will no longer test students on rarely used words. But it will include passages from American historical documents or from writings on freedom and human rights. The College Board says words on the new test will be related to usage. Students will be asked to tell the meaning of words according to the context of the reading passages. Nigerian student Peace Umoru is in her first year at Howard University. She says the rarely used words are the hardest part for internatio...\n\nQ: What's the main idea of the text?", "options": ["How to prepare for the new SAT.", "The SAT will change the entrance test in 2016.", "Advice for foreign students on passing the SAT.", "Tests for entrance to American colleges and universities."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 3017, "question": "The findings of a new survey have American professors talking about the good old days--when A's were a lot tougher to earn. Sites like Rate My Professors.com make it easy for students to find a class taught by a professor who is known as an \"easy grader\".A recent survey by Kaplan Test Prep found that 46 percent of the more than 1,200 students polled admitted to using the site for just such a purpose. \"Our research shows that many of today's college students are looking at multiple factors when picking out courses: overall teacher quality that will result in a good learning experience, but also instructors who don't like to award a lot of C's and D's,\" said Jeff Olson, vice president of research at Kaplan Test Prep. \"While it makes sense that students would choose kinder graders, it also he...\n\nQ: Grade inflation is spreading because    _   .", "options": ["it's poisoning the learning environment", "instructors intend to improve their overall teaching quality", "many instructors adapt to the students' expectations", "students get easy access to sites like RateMyProfessors.com"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2707, "question": "Country singer and songwriter Adrienne Young brings together music and agricultural activities.She even included seeds in the album cover of her first CD. Adrienne Young wants people to know that she supports the movement in America to increase local farming.She offers information about agricultural issues on her Web site.And now part of the moneyfrom her third and newest release, \"Room to Grow\",will be donated to help support community gardens. Adrienne Young's family has lived in Florida for seven generations.Her ancestors helped develop the agriculture industry there.The state of Florida is the nation's second largest producer of fruits and vegetables, 'after California. Adrienne Young has said that her interest in nature was shaped by the fact that she did not grow up on a farm.She gre...\n\nQ: Buying locally grown food has many advantages EXCEPT   _   .", "options": ["it is fresh", "it's tasty", "it's environmental protection", "it raises local production"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 807, "question": "Many people turn to doctors or self-help books, but they forget a great thing that could help them fight illness: their friends. Researchers are only now starting to pay attention to the importance of friendship in health. A 10-year Australian study found that older people with a large circle of friends were 22 percent less likely to die during the study period than those with fewer friends. A large 2007 study showed an increase of nearly 60 percent in the danger for _ among people whose friends gained weight. And last year, Harvard researchers reported that strong social ties could improve brain health as we age. \"In general, the role of friendship in our lives isn't well realized,\" said Rebecca, a professor at the University of North Carolina. \"Friendship has a bigger effect on our psych...\n\nQ: The author mentioned smoking in the text to discuss  _  .", "options": ["the cause of heart attack", "the danger of having no friends", "smoking is bad for men", "friends' influence on habits"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1853, "question": "Treetops, the hotel in the trees, are famous in the world. People know little about Kenya, but they know of Treetops. When King George VI died, Princess Elizabeth was staying on the Treetops, and when she came down from there, \"She _ him as the queen of the country\". The hotel is in the middle of the forest, and it shows the pleasure of Africa. When you visit it, you will be sent into the heart of the forest by hotel buses, and then a guide, with a gun to protect you against big game, will go with you to the Treetops. Before and after dinner, for the whole night if you wish, you can sit on the corridor , watching animals come to the water pool. The earliest hotel Treetops was built round a large tree on the opposite side of the water, but that was destroyed by fire and the new hotel Treeto...\n\nQ: Which of the following statements about \"the cat-like animal\" is WRONG?", "options": ["It comes for food only at night.", "It lives in the trees at Treetops.", "Its teeth and claws can do people harm.", "It can catch any other animal in the forest."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 398, "question": "The Internet has led to a huge increase in credit-card fraud. Your card information could even be for sale in an illegal web site. Web sites offering cheap goods and services should be regarded with care. On-line shoppers who enter their credit-card information may never receive the goods they thought they bought. The thieves then go shopping with your card number -- or sell the information over the Internet. Computers hackers have broken down security systems, raising questions about the safety of cardholder information. Several months ago, 25, 000 customers of CD Universe, an on-line music retailer , were not lucky. Their names, addresses and credit-card numbers were posted on a Web site after the retailer refused to pay US $157, 828 to get back the information. Credit-card firms are now...\n\nQ: How can the thieves get the information of the credit card?", "options": ["The customers give them the information.", "The thieves steal the information from Web sites.", "The customers sell the information to them.", "The thieves buy the information from credit-card firms."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1945, "question": "Artie Shaw was born in New York City in 1910. His name was Arthur Arshawsky. His parents were poor immigrants who had come to the United States from Eastern Europe. His family later moved to New Haven, Connecticut. At the age of fourteen, he began to play the saxophone and then the clarinet. From a very young age, Artie Shaw wanted to play his clarinet better than anyone. He wanted his sound and music to be perfect. He worked at this task much of his life. He began working as a professional musician when he was fifteen. He left home and began playing in bands across the United States. In 1928, young Artie Shaw traveled to Chicago, Illinois to hear the great trumpet player, Louis Armstrong. He immediately understood that Armstrong's great jazz sound was the beginning of something new and ex...\n\nQ: To achieve his music dream, Artie Shaw    _   .", "options": ["first began to play the clarinet", "wanted to be the most famous musician around the world", "began playing in bands across the United States", "became a famous musician when he was fifteen"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1651, "question": "Think of London and you're likely to think of the city's famous bright red double-deckers buses. Think of Thailand's capital city, Bangkok, and the noisy tuk-tuk ( ) may come to mind. Picture the American city of San Francisco and you might see the city's trolleybuses. Imagining what these cities would look like without their red buses, tuk-tuks or trolleybuses is difficult. They are symbols of these cities that make them different from anywhere else in the world. However, these city symbols, which are so loved by tourists, are not always so well loved by their city leaders. City leaders want what is best for their city, which often means the most modern transport. In Thailand, Bangkok city authorities have forbidden new tuk-tuks because they consider them noisy and polluting. However, the...\n\nQ: We can conclude from reading the passage that   _  .", "options": ["tourist cities will lose their charm if their old transport symbols disappear", "a modern city should get rid of inefficient old transport", "old city transport symbols now face the problem of survival", "the writer is in favor of keeping the old city transport symbols"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 988, "question": "Traditionally, women have fallen behind men in adoption of Internet technologies, but a study released yesterday by the Pew Internet & American Life Project found that women under age 65 now get ahead of men in Internet usage, though only by a few percentage points. But the survey also noted that the _ between women and men on the Web is even greater among the 18-to-29 age group and African Americans. The report, \"How Women and Men Use the Internet\", examined use by both sexes, looking at what men and women are doing online as well as their rate of adopting new Web-based technologies. The report found that 86 percent of women aged 18 to 29 were online, compared with 80 percent of men in the same age group. Among African Americans, 60 percent of women are online, compared with 50 percent of...\n\nQ: Among African Americans,   _  .", "options": ["women equal men in the use of the Internet", "women use the Internet less than men", "women use the Internet more than men", "women use the Internet better than men"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2890, "question": "A month after Hurricane Katrina, I returned home in New Orleans. There lay my house, reduced towaist-high ruins, smelly and dirty. Before the trip, I'd had my car fixed. When the office employee of the garage was writing up the bill,she noticed my Louisiana license plate. \"You from New Orleans?\"she asked I said I was, \"No charge.\"She said, and firmly shook her head when I reached for my wallet. The next day I went for a haircut, and the same thing happened. As my wife was studying in Florida, we decided to move there and tried to find a rental house that we could afford while also paying off a mortgage (> on our mined house. We looked at many places, but none was satisfactory. We'd began to accept that we*d have to live in extremely reduced circumstances for a while, when I got a very curi...\n\nQ: The author learned from his experience that  _", "options": ["worldly possessions can be given up when necessary", "generosity should be encouraged in some cases", "people benefit from their sad stories", "human beings are kind after all."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 3224, "question": "\"For those who haven't been to Tibet is a dream; for those who have already been there, Tibet is a memory.\" said Li Wan, a graduate from Zhongshan University. \"For me, living there is my dream and happiness.\" Li was suddenly crazy about Tibet after working there for three months as an office clerk. Since 2008, Li has spent most of her time travelling in Tibet. Four years have passed and she has been almost every corner of Tibet. Li came to Tibet firstly because of her desire for personal freedom. She entered Tibet along the Yunnan-Tibetan road, enjoying the special view happily. She was surprised to find that it is a white paradise on earth. Although she couldn't even speak a word of Tibetan language, she had no difficulty in communicating with natives. \"To me, they are free, generous, sim...\n\nQ: During the adventures in Tibet, what Li Wan learned most is   _  .", "options": ["to enjoy the beauty of nature", "to get along well with natives", "to follow her heart to live her life", "to set down journals about travel"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1309, "question": "History is full of cases where dreams have been a pathway to creativity and discovery. A striking example is provided by Dr. Otto Loewi, a pharmacologist and winner of a Nobel Prize. Loewi had spent years studying the chemical transmission of nerve impulses . A major breakthrough in his research came when he dreamed of an experiment three nights in a row. On the first two nights he woke up and wrote down the experiment quickly and untidily on paper. But the next morning, he couldn't tell what the notes meant. On the third night, he got up after having the dream. This time, instead of making notes he went straight to his laboratory and performed the important experiment. Loewi later said that if the experiment had occurred to him while awake he would not have given it another thought. Loewi...\n\nQ: Through Loewi's experiment, the author tries to prove that   _  .", "options": ["very little is really known about the meaning of dreams", "dreams can be useful in producing creative solutions to one's problems", "it is possible to \"catch\" one's dreams by planning before going to sleep", "it helped in the study of transmission of nerve impulses"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2125, "question": "In America, drivers' education is part of the regular high school curriculum . Every student in his or her second year of high school is required to take a class in driver's education. However, unlike other courses, it is not given during the regular school year. Instead it is a summer course. The course is divided up into two parts: class time for learning laws and regulations, and driving time to practice driving. Class time is not unlike any other class. The students study the basic traffic laws from a text to pass the written driving test that is given to anyone who wants to get a driver's license. Driving time is a chance for the students to get behind the wheel and practice starting steering, backing up, parking, switching lanes, turning corners, and all the other maneuvers required ...\n\nQ: Which of the following is Not True for the students wanting to get their driver's license?", "options": ["They must have their eyes examined.", "They must be 16 years of age.", "They should go to have their driver's test.", "They ought to do well in their driver's course."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1898, "question": "Mary Master man, a senior at West Moore High School in prefix = st1 /Oklahoma City, was named the winner Tuesday of the annual Intel Science Talent Search. More than 1,700 high school seniors across the nation entered the competition, which is in its 66th year. Spectrographs, which measure wave lengths, are used in research such as astronomy and medicine and in industry. For example, they can be used as a sensing equipment to look for explosives or drugs or to help determine how old an art work is through its powders. They can cost as much as $100,000, but Masterman's invention--made of lenses, a laser, aluminum tubing and a camera--cost less than $1,000, Intel said. Masterman received the honor from Intel Corp. Chairman Craig Barrett during a banquet Tuesday night inWashington. \"It was a ...\n\nQ: What is probably the best title for the passage?", "options": ["Senior challenges Nobel prize.", "Masterman invents a sensing equipment.", "Teen wins $100,000 science scholarship.", "Spectrograph recognizes the \"fingerprints\"."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1504, "question": "Columbus made four voyages to the west between 1492 and 1504 in his vain search for a sea route to Asia. The mystery of why he failed to find it haunted him and filled him with sadness. Wherever he went to Cuba, Puerto Rico, Jamaica, South America, Panama, down the coast of Central America--it was always the same story. Instead of golden palaces, there were grass huts and palm-leaf tents. Instead of silk-robed merchant princes, he found \"Indians\" who did not have so much as a shirt on their backs. When Columbus explored the West Indies in 1493,he heard tales of a fierce Indian tribe who literally devoured its defeated enemies after a battle. These people were called by many names in the area, including Calina, Canima, Carib, and Caniba. Columbus recorded the name of the American natives as...\n\nQ: Columbus thought that   _  .", "options": ["others had sailed to Asia before him", "it was impossible to sail to Asia", "the land he had found was not China or Japan", "the geographers knew about the land he had found"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 228, "question": "He looked like a pirate. With his handkerchief tied in a knot behind his little nine-year-old head, he looked like a pirate, a sad pirate. The first time little David came to our camp, he was hairless and worn out from medical treatments. He was also very angry. Paul Newman's camp counselors ( ) were hoping to fill David's days with fun and laughter. But David stayed inside himself, wanting to be alone, or in a corner of the cabin. At this camp for children with life-threatening illnesses, we had seen some pretty tough children worn out by cancer recover full of energy despite their illness. But we saw little progress in David no matter what we tried with him. Five days into the eight-day session saw a quiet, sad little pirate. Then something happened on that fifth night. Something at camp...\n\nQ: Which of the following does NOT show the change in David?", "options": ["David came back to the camp for a second session after the first ended.", "David had become quite ill and had to go to the hospital because of this new crisis.", "David made his way from counselor to counselor to say an early good-bye to camp.", "David stood in front of me and gave me a hug and a big wet kiss on my cheek."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 3404, "question": "My mother, Marisol Torres, came with her family to Australia in the early 1960s. Then my parents' marriage ended and Mum began the study of precious stones. Her interest in opals took her to the New South Wales remote town of Lightning Ridge. There were no luxuries , but she was closer to nature and had a chance to find black opals and make some money. My mother was beautiful with dark hair and brown eyes, but she was also quiet and shy. Early in the Ridge years, she kept to herself, but later, she started going to the neighbourhood centre to make friends. It was her dream to mine, but her get-rich-quick thinking was unrealistic. She was cheated and she was never very successful. But she kept a sense of humour and a charming smile. Then, just as friendships began to blossom, she was diagno...\n\nQ: After the author's mother died, she fulfilled her desire by   _  .", "options": ["treating her mother's Ridge friends with Spanish food", "writing a biography about her whole life", "decorating her house in Lightning Ridge", "finding a lot of black opals in Lightning Ridge"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 1312, "question": "Mountaineers have noted that as they climb, for example, up to the 12,633foot Humphreys Peak in Arizona, plant life changes greatly. In the Sonoran Desert, one climbs into a pine forest at 7,000 feet and a treeless tundra on the top of the mountain. It may seem that plants at a given altitude are associated in what can be called \"communities\" -groupings of species. The idea is that over time, plants that require particular climate and soil conditions come to live in the same places, and are frequently to be found together. Scientists study the history of plant life and build up a picture of how groups of plants have responded to climate changes and how ecosystems develop. But are these associations, _ are real in the present, permanent? A great natural experiment took place on this planet ...\n\nQ: According to the passage, the movement of individual species of plants   _  .", "options": ["occurs in groups", "often depends upon the formation of lakes", "does not occur in groups", "depends upon climate and soil conditions"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2442, "question": "Most of us spend our lives seeking the natural world.We go fishing,sit in the garden,have a picnic,live in the suburbs or go to the seaside.The most popular leisure activity in Britain is going for a walk.When joggers jog,they don't run the streets.Every one of them tend to go to the park or the river. But despite this,our children are growing up nature deprived .I spent my boyhood climbing trees.These days,children are robbed of these ancient freedoms,due to problems like crime,traffic,the loss of the open spaces and strange new ideas about what is best for children,that is to say,things that can be bought,rather than things that can be found. The truth is to be found elsewhere.A study in the US: families had moved to better housing and the children were assessed for ADHD--attention defic...\n\nQ: In what way do people benefit from their contact with nature?", "options": ["Children with ADHD can be cured.", "A garden nearby improves the quality of old people's life.", "Problems with crime and violent behavior will easily be solved.", "Children's performance at school is greatly improved."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 207, "question": "College is a fresh start, and a chance to make new friends. These friends may become your lifelong friends, or the person you want to spend the rest of your life with. Whether you are going to a nearby college or the university far away from home, you are likely to meet new people wherever you are. Here are some advice to help you make friends at college. Clearly, your classmates are all possible friends! Get to class early on the first day, and if you get there early enough, you will be in the room, or waiting outside it, with one other person, or a small group. A good casual opener would be to ask if you're in the right classroom, then introduce yourself, and explain that you're new, and a _ . Do this at all of your classes, and you will have a group of friends that you can make study gr...\n\nQ: According to the text, the friends you get to know in class may   _  .", "options": ["share your interests", "invite you to parties", "help you to become a good player", "take notes for you"], "answer": 3}]